翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
Let's talk course logistics.
我们来谈谈课程后勤吧
This isn't a fun topic.
这个话题有点无聊
But for those of you who are taking this class for credit,
但是如果你需要通过这门课获得学分
this stuff will probably be important to you.
这些内容特别重要
Everybody else, maybe you skip it.
也许其他人可以跳过它
I'll note that the slide is green.
这张幻灯片是绿色的
So if you're someone who is watching the webcasts,
所以如果你是在看网络直播的人
because you prefer to see the live version of this,
因为你更喜欢看实况转播的版本
these will always be green.
这些将永远是绿色的
So you can easily find it if you're skimming through a 50 minute video.
你可以快速从50分钟的视频中找到它
So course logistics-- first of all, we have a bunch of different places to get information.
所以课程后勤...首先，我们可以从很多不同的地方来获取资源
So we have this course website here, which is Data Structures, very clever.
我们有一个课程网站，它很智能
We Actually, in keeping with tradition, we would have done since 61b.org.
其实网址最开始是61b.org
But somebody sniped it. And I guess it's available for sale.
但是被人攻击了，我猜是想售卖它
But I will never reward domain snipers.
不过我不会花钱讨好这个攻击域名的
So that's going to be the main place where everything is.
所以在这里存放了所有的资源
And I encourage you to go there to find everything.
我鼓励你们来这里寻找一切
We will also have lectures, which I'm doing here.
我们还有课程讲解，就像现在这样
There's also webcasts for the live lecture each semester,
每学期还会有线下课程的网络直播
so that you can see what really happened in the room.
这样你就能看到教室里的情况
We have a Piazza discussion forum.
我们有一个 Piazza 论坛
We have office hours that are in 109 Morgan.
办公时我们在摩根大楼109室
And then we also, of course, have our various places where we get together.
同样还有一起讨论的各种地方
We have lab and discussion.
我们有实验和讨论
And in addition to these scheduled times for lab and discussion,
除了这些预定的实验和讨论外
we'll also have Guerrilla Sections, which will be special discussion sections we'll talk about later,
我们还会有随时的讨论，稍后会提到
which are mastery learning based where you work in groups until everybody gets the problem.
这是一种基于团队学习的方法，让每个人都发现问题
We'll have group tutoring sessions for those of you who want a little extra help five on one or even one on one.
我们会为那些需要额外帮助的人提供小组辅导，五对一甚至一对一
And then there's also this little textbook, which I don't have a name for it yet.
还有这个小课本，我还没想好它的名字
So it's just called Hug61B for now.
暂时叫它 Hug61B
And that is linked just on the main page.
课本的链接就在主页上
These readings here are part of that little text.
这里的读物是小课本的一部分
And the goal with that was just to build a free online resource that was really tailored to 61B.
这样做的目的只是为了建立一个为 61B 独身定制的免费在线资源
If you don't really like it, there's alternate readings on the Spring '16 version of the course that you can check out instead.
如果你真的不喜欢它，可以去看这门课16年春版的读物
So that's all the official places you can get information for this course.
以上就是这门课官方提供的资源
And then of course, there are a bunch of unofficial channels.
当然，还有很多非官方渠道
I welcome you, as you're working through the class, to go googling for things.
你们正在学习这门课，我欢迎你们去搜索相关的东西
Though of course, please do not google solutions to the homeworks.
当然了，别去搜作业的答案
Because you will not learn things by looking at them. It won't work out well.
因为只看是学不会的，没什么好结果
So if you are somebody enrolled in the class and you're on the wait list,
对于注册了这门课或者在候补名单里的学生
if you do project zero, I'll do whatever I can to get you in by week four.
如果你做项目0，我会尽量让你在第四周前进去
I don't have a lot of power to get people into the class.
我其实无权让人们进入这个班级
But I can at least tell people to, I don't know, try and do something.
但我至少可以试着做点什么
This week or at least at the beginning in the class,
本周或者在课程刚开始时
the morning sections are going to be really popular and the evening ones, less so.
早上的时间段会很受欢迎，而晚上却远不如此
So if you don't have a particular discussion or lab, you can go to any section or lab.
所以如果你没有特定的讨论或实验，去哪个时间段都行
But if you are already enrolled in a section,
但是如果你已经注册了一个时间段
I ask that you try and go to the one that you're officially registered for.
你就必须去注册的那个
That way, we don't get super overcrowded.
这样我们才不会人满为患
That's especially important in the lab.
这点要求对于实验尤其重要
So maybe hover outside the room for the first two minutes before the class starts.
所以也许你可以在上课前的两分钟在教室外面徘徊
And then if there's room, go on in.
如果有位置就进去吧
And then after attendance settles, you can do whatever you want.
出席率稳定后，规定就没有那么严格了
But for now, while things are crowded, make sure to be courteous to your fellow student.
但是现在教室很拥挤时，一定要对同学有礼貌
If you do get to a section and it's super full, priority will go to those who are officially registered.
假如你真的碰到满员的教室，应该让正式注册的人优先进入
If you have any administrative issues, we ask that you post it to the discussion forums.
有管理方面的问题可以发布到论坛上
Or if you'd like, you can send an email to cs61b@berkeley.
或者发邮件到 cs61b@berkeley
What I ask is you don't email me directly with logistical issues, because I won't be as helpful as somebody else.
但是不要给我发邮件报告后勤问题，我不会像其他人那样有帮助
Because I'm probably just going to send you to someone else anyway.
因为不管怎样，我可能都会把你交给别人来处理
And the other thing is that with over 1,000 students,
另外我们有1000多名学生
if you actually do the math, if I were to say, hey, everybody come meet me for just one minute,
你算一算，如果每个人都来见我一分钟
that would take 22 hours to complete that process.
一共要花22个小时
So logistical emails, you know, even if they're taking only a small amount of time, it adds up.
所以有关后勤的邮件，即使每封不长但加起来就很费时间了
Now, as far as the course goes, perhaps more interesting to you,
现在我们讨论课程，你们应该更感兴趣
this course is broken into three parts.
本课程分为三个部分
This is the new vision for 61B that I tried out last spring.
这是去年春季 61B 新版本中的尝试
So the first part is an introduction to Java that's oriented around data structures.
第一部分面向数据结构介绍 Java 语言
What we're going to do is learn Java in the context of building lists.
我们在构建 List 的过程中学习 Java
So if used lists in some language like Python before,
如果之前你使用过某种语言（比如 Python）的 List
in this class we're going to kick off learning Java by thinking about different ways to build lists.
本门课将通过用不同的方式构建 List 来快速学习 Java
And that will give us the syntax we need to move forward.
这会为我们的进度补充所需语法
So what we're going to have during this time,
所以在这段时间里
we have an optional homework 0 that's already out that I encourage you to do if you haven't yet.
我们已经发布了选修作业0，如果你没有使用过 Java 编程，我鼓励你做一下
We will have three labs during this period
这部分有三个实验
that are going to introduce you to all the real world tools we're going to be using throughout the semester.
会介绍这个学期将使用的真实工具
And I'll warn you in advance it's going to be annoying.
提醒你们，这些很无聊
Things are not going to work at first.
万事开头难
You're going to have to beat your head against the wall.
只要肯攀登
But I think that's a really important thing for you to learn how to do.
但这很重要，你必须学会使用
So I've resisted the urge to try and just write the master installer that just installs everything.
因此我忍住不去写一个安装器来安装好所有的东西
Because I think it is really important that you know how to deal with the messiness of, say,
因为你需要知道如何处理乱七八糟的事情，比方说
the command line and installing software and getting things working.
命令行、软件安装或让程序运行起来
Because you'll be doing it forever.
你早晚要面临
Then we'll also have two projects, projects 0 on 1.
我们还会有两个项目，项目0和项目1
And those are going to be our programming homework during that period, a couple of little projects.
这两个小项目是这部分的编程作业
Phase 2 will be the advanced programming part of the class.
第二阶段是高级编程部分
And this is the part where you're going to really get a chance to design something.
你真正有机会设计一些东西
You're going to work in a team of people, a pair of people, kind of.
你要在团队中工作，准确讲是两个人
We'll talk about how it's a little more complicated much later.
我们将在很久以后讨论它是如何变得更复杂的
But basically, you'll work with group of people to come up with a design to solve a problem.
不过你基本会和一群人共同思考一个问题解决方法的设计
So unlike programming classes you might have had before where it's,
这跟你之前的编程课程会很不一样
well, fill in this function that does this thing,
比如实现某个功能的函数
here syou're going to have to design the architecture.
然而在这里，你将不得不设计架构
And I think you'll find it really challenging.
我想你会发现这真的很有挑战性
And this is the part of the class where it will really,
这是课程的一部分
for those of you who are average to below average programmers,
对于中下水平的程序员来说
this part will be really hard.
这部分真的很难
I'm just warning you in advance. But it's good for you.
我只是提前警告你，但这对你有好处
I'm not doing it to weed you out or scare you away.
我这么做不是为了让你避而远之
I'm doing it, because I want to built you into being really independent programmers,
是因为我想把你们打造成真正独立的程序员
to set the bar high enough and make you realize you can do something you didn't know you knew how to do.
把门槛设得足够高，让你做一些不知道该怎么做的事情
So that big project will be due March 6.
那个大项目截止日期是3月6号
And there will be some labs to help support that project.
将会有一些实验为这个项目提供帮助
So we'll do a little peer design reviews.
我们会进行同行审阅
And we'll talk more about that later.
稍后再详细讨论这一点
OK. Premiere is installing, good.
好的，Pr 正在启动
In the final phase of the class is our standard data structures and algorithms class.
课程的最后阶段数据结构和算法
Uh-oh, I don't want to do this right now, Premiere. We'll get to it later.
哎呀，我现在不想使用 Pr，一会再说
So weeks 8 through 14,
所以第8周到第14周
we're going to learn about what a hash table is, what binary search trees are, all of this classic stuff that goes in a data structures class.
我们将学习什么是哈希表、二叉搜索树，数据结构课程中所有经典的内容
And during that time, each of the labs is going to implement some data structure algorithm.
在此期间，每个实验都将实现一些数据结构算法
And each of those labs, whenever you go in person, the last, say, 10 to 20 minutes, depending on how things work out,
每次你亲自去做实验，根据实际情况最后10分钟到20分钟
the TA will lead you through a good implementation of that thing.
助教会引导你顺利完成
So it'll be a chance to reflect on what you've just done.
这是一个机会来反思之前做的事情
And the lab should be self-contained.
而且实验应该是独立进行的
So it shouldn't feel like an extra homework.
这不应看作是额外的作业
It's just a chance to really think about a particular implementation.
而是一个思考（数据结构）特定实现的机会
We also have homeworks during that period.
那段时间我们也有作业
And each one of those homeworks is going to be to apply a data structure or algorithm.
每个作业都将去应用一种数据结构或算法
So rather than implementing a hash table, you'll use them for something.
也就是说不是让你实现哈希表，而是使用它完成一些事情
And I hope that you'll find it interesting.
我希望你会觉得有趣
And so there will be two of these.
所以会有两个这样的
Two of these homeworks are going to be released after classes are over.
其中两项作业将在下课后发布
And those you can think of as extra practice or makeups for homeworks you missed earlier.
而那些你可以认为是你之前错过的额外练习或补习
And I'll talk more about the drop policies and grading in a moment.
稍后我会更多地谈到降价政策和评分
And during that time, there will be one medium sized data structure and algorithms project
这部分还有一个中型的数据结构和算法项目
where you don't have to do all the architecture,
你不需要做所有的架构
but you will have to select the data structures and think carefully about how to organize your code.
但必须选择数据结构并仔细考虑如何组织代码
And you'll have to implement an algorithm that will allow you to traverse a graph.
还要实现一个遍历图的算法
You'll learn what that means later.
之后你会了解的
And so if you're curious, you can look at the calendar to see how these three phases work and look at the whole schedule.
所以如果你好奇的话，可以在日历中浏览这三个阶段，然后再看看整个时间表
But I won't talk about them more now.
现在就不再多讲了
So as far as what you have to do each week, there are labs.
你们每周都要做实验
And these labs are required.
这些实验是必需的
It's OK to work on the labs ahead of time.
最好提前做实验
And while the work in the labs is required for the course,
本课程中所要求的实验
being in person is not required.
不需要亲自到场
So if you want, you can do the labs from home. And that's fine.
所以只要你愿意，你可以在家做实验
But especially if you're somebody who does not feel like a strong programmer,
但是尤其是那些认为自己不太优秀的人
I think you'll find them hopefully really helpful, especially at the beginning when you're trying to get things set up.
你会发现它们很有帮助，特别是你一开始就想把事情做好
There will be some special project labs where attendance is required.
有一些必须参加的特殊实验
Those will be a little later.
那是很晚的事情了
And I'll talk about those in a different lecture.
我会在另一节课上讲
But be aware you can do things from home.
知道可以在家实验就行了
Labs are always going to be due Friday at 5:00.
实验一般截止到周五下午5点
So that way, you know, it's done.
到时候你就知道快结束了
And you weekend can begin.
你的周末随即开始
And then there's also some labs, by the way, that are freebies.
顺便说一下，还有一些实验是免费的
There will be one lab in particular which is just, go work on project two.
有一个特殊的实验是在第二个项目上工作
And you'll get free points for that one. You don't even have to show up.
甚至不用露面你都可以获得免费的分数
And then we're going to have-- OK, sorry.
然后我们会有...抱歉
And so summarizing for the labs are all out.
这里是实验的总结
We have 14 of those.
一共有14个实验
They're worth 4 points each.
每个4分
And that's going to come to 48 points.
一共48分
The reason that it doesn't come to more points than that is because we're going to drop your lowest two.
之所以加起来不是64分，是因为会去掉两个最低分
That's intended to cover any life difficulties.
这是为了应付生活中的困难
So because we have so many students,
因为我们的学生太多了
these drops are supposed to handle your life emergencies.
这样做可以处理生活中的紧急情况
So the thing where you're about to submit your code,
比如你要提交代码时
but then your computer crashed or your internet went out or whatever it may be, sorry.
你点电脑死机了或者网络断了，也可能是其他原因
I know that's a bummer.
这一定令人很失望
You did this work, and you're not getting credit for it.
你完成了工作却没有得到奖励
But we're going to drop two labs,
但我们舍弃了两个实验
so that those kind of emergencies get smoothed out.
这样紧急情况就会得到缓解
Now, if you have some kind of really big life crisis that's bigger than two weeks,
如果你的麻烦超过两周
of course, we'll work with you and make sure things are better.
我们会和你一起解决
But for the run of the mill, you know,
但是一般情况为了课程进行
dog ate my homework situations, that's what the drops are for.
狗吃了我的作业情况 这就是滴水的用处
They're not intended to be, well, I didn't want to do some of the work.
他们不是故意的 嗯 我不想做一些工作
Discussions those will also be happening once a week.
每周还会有一次讨论
And those will be an hour each.
每次一个小时
Attendance for these is not required.
这些活动不需要出席
But you can earn a gold point for every discussion you go to.
但是每参加一次都可以获得一个黄金分数
And I'll explain what those are in a moment.
稍后我会解释这些是什么
Also, attendance is not taken the first two weeks.
此外，前两周的讨论出席忽略不计
You can't get your gold points then.
你拿不到黄金分数
But after that, you'll be able to accumulate these gold points.
不过在那之后，你可以开始积累了
And basically what they are is they're extra credit.
根本上讲，它们是额外的学分
But it's extra credit that the worst you do on the exams, the more of the gold points count up to a maximum of double.
你考得越差黄金分数越多，最高达到两倍
So if you go to 10 discussions and you get zero on the exams,
假设你参加了10次讨论，考试却得了0分
you will get 20 points added to your final score.
你的最终分数将增加20分
Now, it is not an advantageous strategy to intentionally get zeros on the exams.
故意考0分不太明智
That will not work out in your favor as you'll see in the point totals later.
这没有好处，一会在积分总和中就能看到
But it's basically just another little way,
但其实这是另外一个小方式
so that if you're somebody who's really struggling,
如果你真的学得很挣扎
you can demonstrate your participation in the course
这可以证明你参加了这门课程
and let us know that you're really trying and you're thinking about things.
而且真的在很努力思考
And that will give us some measure of the fact that you're doing well in the course,
这个方式可以让我们知道你表现得不错
even if you maybe have trouble on some exam problem you get stuck on.
即便你考试时陷入困境
We have homeworks.
我们还有作业
So there's going to be seven total for-credit works in the class, homeworks one through seven.
这门课一共有7个作业，作业1到7
And there's also this optional homework zero already available.
另外选修作业0已经可以开始做了
Homeworks two to seven are all about using data structures and algorithms to solve some problem.
作业2到7全是使用数据结构和算法来解决问题
And homework one is basically going to be as we transition into advanced programming,
作业1是我们过渡到高级编程时
it's a little mini assignment you do before you kick off that big design project that I alluded to.
我之前提到的大项目前的一个小任务
So these due dates are going to vary.
这些截至日期不太一样
They're not going to be due any particular day. Make sure to check the calendar.
它们没有特定的截止日期，一定要好好看看日历
And so of the seven homeworks, we're going to drop two.
7个作业中我们会忽略2个
And since they're worth 16 points, that comes to 80 points total.
所以每个作业16分但最终累积80分
And again, these are intended to cover life difficulties.
再说一次，这些都是为了解决生活中的困难
So if you have problems, the drops are supposed to handle these.
忽略2个作业可以处理问题
As I mentioned earlier, homeworks six and seven are actually going to be released during the recitation week at the end of the semester.
我之前提到过，作业6和7实际上是在期末复习周发布的
So again, you can think of it as practice if you want.
所以你愿意的话，可以把它们当作是练习
And if you missed an early homework,
如果你错过了早期的作业
you can then do those homeworks to make up for something you missed earlier.
你就要做这2个作业来弥补
And then lastly, we have our projects.
最后，我们有自己的项目
And so the projects in 61B are fairly famous in terms of being really challenging.
61B 的项目在挑战性方面很有名
You know, there's some infamy surrounding past projects, like Gitlet and Editor.
你可能知道过去像 Gitlet 和 Editor 这样的项目很讨人厌
And in this semester, I think that will be no exception.
这学期也不例外
Though I'm hoping this semester that for programmers who don't have a lot of experience,
不过在这学期，对于没有太多经验的程序员来说
I'm really hoping to not annihilate you and make your lives miserable.
我真的希望这些项目不会消灭你们，困扰你的生活
And we'll, of course, keep in contact.
当然我们可以随时联系
Because this class was always a delicate balancing act.
这门课保持着一个微妙的平衡
Because I want to make it really hard,
我想让它变得很难
but I don't want to make it miserable.
但不至于让人太痛苦
And so we'll be working together to make sure it works well.
所以我们要共同努力让事情正常运行
So projects, two of them are team projects.
其中2个项目是团队项目
So project zero, which will be released on the first Friday of class, that's going to be 25 points.
项目0将在开课的第一个周五发布，值25分
Then we'll have a solo project that's 40 points.
紧接着会有一个40分的个人项目
That's going to be a two-week project.
这是个为期两周的项目
Then there's going to be this team project.
然后会有一个团队项目
It will be a three-week design project.
这是一个为期三周的设计项目
And then finally, we come around to the solo and final project, which is 75 points.
最后还有一个单人项目，值75分
So these are small, medium, and large.
这是小型、中型、大型项目
And on the solo projects, all of your work needs to be your own.
单人项目中的所有工作都要独自完成
I'll be elaborating a bit more in a future lecture about what exactly your own work means.
未来某堂课上我会更详细地说明单人工作的意义
But if you'd like to read it now, you can check out the collaboration policy on the website.
但是如果你现在就想知道，可以在网站上看看合作的政策
And it's always OK to talk to other students in the class and help them debug and even bounce ideas back and forth.
与班上学生交谈、帮助他们调试、甚至彼此反馈想法都是可以的
But your code really needs to be in your work.
但是你的代码只能为自己所用
And then I'll mention also that these last two projects two and three, they have extra credit opportunities.
另外，最后两个项目有额外的学分机会
If you turn in the code early enough that you pass the early submission tests--
尽早提交代码可以进行早期测试
so basically, there will be some early tests And if you get those right, you'll get some bonus points.
通过早期测试就会获得加分
You'll get some bonus points.
你会得到加分的
And then both of those projects, there will also be some stretch goals, like extra hard things you can do that will earn you some gold points.
项目也有一些延伸的目标，会为你提供一些黄金分数
And that's the story with projects.
这就是关于项目的事情
And we have exams.
我们还有考试
So exams in this class are going to be hard.
这门课的考试会很难
If you've taken 61A, you know what that is like.
如果你上过 61A 你知道那是什么滋味
And you'll get used to this in the academic environment at Berkeley.
以后你会在伯克利的学术环境中习惯这一点
So the exams are targeted around a median of around 60%.
考试的目标中位数是60%左右
And so 60%, the point there is not to crush you and say you know nothing, right?
60%并不是为了压垮你让你知道自己很失败
Because if you came from high school,
想一想你高中的时候
60 is like the worst grade you can imagine depending on where you're from.
60分几乎是你能想象的到最差的分数了
But if you're from the United States, 60 would be like, I don't know, I'm in trouble.
在美国，如果我得了60分那我就有麻烦了
Like my parents are going to kick in my door and set fire to my bed.
我爸妈可能会踢开房门烧毁我的被子
I don't know, whatever it is that parents tend to do.
我不确定他们做什么
Probably not arson in their own homes, though.
也许不会在自己家里放火
But anyway, the point of the 60% medians is to let you know what you don't know, which is a little different.
但不管怎样，60%的中位数是为了让你知道你不知道的东西，这有点不同
That's to say there's still more to go.
也就是说还有很长的路要走
You haven't mastered everything.
你知道的还少呢
And there are students that, even though the median is around 60, that get up in the 90s on these exams.
尽管中位数在60分左右，但还是会有一些学生考到90分
And it's a way to make sure that everybody really has a fair grade.
这是一种确保每个人都有相对公平分数的方法
Because of the exams of 90 is what's considered good, then someone who does great,
因为90岁的考试被认为是好的 那么做得好的人
they have no way to demonstrate that.
他们没有办法证明这一点
They have no way to get the feedback to know that, yes, you're really doing super well.
没有反馈告诉他们，你真的做得非常好
And that's something that's important to us here, to really give you a sense of what it is that you can strive for.
这对我们来说很重要 让你们真正了解你们可以为之奋斗的东西是什么
Now, what's interesting is that students often, as I mentioned in the previous video,
现在 有趣的是 正如我在前面的视频中提到的 学生们经常
had this mental model that some students are destined for greatness and some are not.
有这样一种心理模式 即一些学生注定会成就伟业 而另一些学生则不然
And that is really not what this exam process is about.
而这真的不是这个考试过程的目的
It's not about like separating out those who have like the special magical piece in their brain that makes them do well.
这并不是说要把那些喜欢他们大脑中让他们做得很好的特殊魔力的人分开
Because my suspicion, based on education research,
因为我怀疑，教育研究表明
is that if you had the resources and the time and you approach studying appropriately,
如果你有足够的资源和时间，并且学习方式得当
probably most everybody in this class could get into the 90s on the exams.
可能这个班的大多数人都能考到90多分
Anyway, it won't happen, but it could.
不管怎么说 这不会发生 但有可能
And it's only, you know, our failure as instructors in some ways that we don't get you all there. Sorry.
我们老师在某些方面做得不够好，没能把你们都带到那种水平，抱歉
But we'll do what we can.
但我们会尽力而为
So then with these exams, we're going to have two midterms.
我们会有两次期中考试
They're in the evenings.
安排在晚上
And there'll be one final exam.
还有一次期末考试
And then they're closed notes, closed book, but you can bring one sheet of handwritten notes per exam.
考试是封闭式的，但每次考试你都可以带一张手写笔记
So for the first exam, you get one sheet,
所以第一次考试 你会拿到一张纸
second exam you get two, third you get three.
第二次考试得两次 第三次考试得三次
And there is one extra neat thing, which is that we actually have a policy.
我们还有一个比较好的政策
Especially given the fact that we know that many of you are trying to get into the major and your grades really matter,
特别是考虑到你们中的许多人都在努力进入这个专业，成绩真的很重要
if your midterm grades are worse than you do on your finals statistically, we can replace your midterm score.
如果你的期中成绩比期末成绩差，我们可以替换你的期中成绩
So we have a specific mechanical process.
我们有一个机械的流程
You can read all about it on the website.
你可以在网站上读到关于它的所有内容
But basically if you have a bad early midterm that doesn't doom you,
大概就是如果期中考试考得很糟糕不意味着完蛋了
the final can actually help you recover using a process we call shadowing.
期末考试可以帮助你来恢复一些，我们称这个过程为影子
The exam dates-- so this date is confirmed.
考试日期已经确定了
This is Valentine's Day from 7:00 to 9:00 PM.
情人节晚上7点到9点
Sorry. That's the only date I was able to get that fit. I tried.
对不起，就那一天比较合适，我争取过了
They almost gave me the day before.
他差一点就把前一天给我
But then they said we'd have to have 20 exam rooms.
但是后来他们说我们得有20个考场
And I actually said that's fine.
其实我说过没问题
But then I don't know. Then they decided that didn't want to give us that many rooms.
然后后来他们又不想给我们那么多房间了
And so that'll be the exam time.
所以就定在那天考试
And the drop deadline will be February 17 for the course.
退课的截止日期是2月17日
So this semester is a very special semester for many of you.
这个学期对你们很多人来说很特别
Because how you do in this class may make the difference between really getting into computer science or not.
因为在这门课上的表现可能会决定你是否真正走入计算机科学的大门
And so as a result, we want to make sure you get feedback on this first exam.
所以我希望你在第一次考试后得到反馈
We'll actually have advising sessions in between the midterm and this drop deadline.
我们会在期中考试和这个截止日期前进行开启咨询
so you can make a decision about whether or not to drop the class.
这样你就可以决定是否退课了
Because once that drop deadline passes, you're pretty much committed.
而一旦过了退课的截止日期，你就只能全力以赴了
So you want to make sure that if you're somebody that's really passionate about computer science,
所以你要确保自己是一个真正对计算机科学充满热情的人
but you've struggled, we want to make sure that we can let you know you need a little more time to catch up before you really give 61B a shot.
但如果你一直很挣扎，我们要保证让你知道，你还需要一段时间才能来尝试61B
So that's the point.
以上就是重点
And that's why, sorry, we have to ruin your Valentine's Day.
也是我们不得不毁掉你们情人节的原因
Midterm two will be March 22 probably.
第二次中期考试大概是3月22日
But I haven't gotten this confirmed.
但我还不是很确定
And then the final will definitely be May 10 at 7:00 PM.
但期末考试一定是5月10日的晚上7点
Now, if you're somebody that has alternate exam times,
如果你有多个考试时间
we will accommodate you.
我们会为你安排
Don't email me directly, as I mentioned earlier.
我说过不要给我发邮件
We'll actually provide a forum. Because we know there's lots of people.
我们会提供一个论坛，因为学生太多了
Some people have exam conflicts with the finals, because we have overlapping lecture times.
有些人考试会有冲突，因为课程之间有重叠
And just things happen.
然后事情就发生了
With 1,300 people, you can't help but have alternate exam times.
1300人必须安排多个考试时间
So we will have a form.
我们有一张表格
Don't worry yet.
先别担心
We'll send up the information when it's time.
到时候我们会把信息发上去的
So to summarize all of this, these are all the things you do in this class.
总之，以上就是你们在这堂课上要做的所有事情
You have labs and homeworks that will help you understand the basics of the class.
实验和作业可以帮助你理解课程的基础知识
We have projects that I'm hoping will build you into independent programmers.
项目可以把你们培养成独立的程序员
And they're worth a lot more points.
而且他们分数更多
Then we have our midterms and finals to assess how well you understood the theoretical content of the class.
期中和期末考试可以评估你们对课程理论内容的理解程度
And so the reason, by the way, these homeworks and labs are not weighted very much is they're not intended to evaluate your competence.
顺便说一句，作业和实验的比重不大是因为它们不是用来评估你能力的
They're there to help you build your skills.
它们是帮助你培养技能的
Projects actually serve sort of a dual role.
项目实际上起到了双重作用
So you can get credit for the project or the programming work you're doing, and you can also learn at the same time.
这样你就可以从正在做的项目或编程工作中获得学分，同时你也可以从中学到东西
So overall, there are 768 points you can earn.
你一共可以获得768分
And there's also extra credit points.
而且还有额外的学分
And the website details how there's 16 total extra credit points that involve surveys and yada, yada.
网站详细说明了额外的16个学分，涉及调研等等
And that's the score you get.
这些就是你可以得到的分数
So at the end of the class, the way we assign grades is we take your total score,
在课程结束时，我们会计算你们的总分
and then we compare it to a bunch of bends.
然后我们把它比作一堆弯道
The course website shows every single bend,
课程网站显示了每一个弯道
but I've just given the highlights here.
我在这里也总结了一下
So if you need a C minus, there's 368 points you need to earn.
也就说如果C-需要368分
We don't really typically do anything more complicated than that.
我们不会弄得更复杂了
You know, occasionally when someone's like barely, barely, barely, on the border,
有的人非常非常非常接近边界
and they've been just really truly wonderful on Piazza,
他在 Piazza 表现得特别好
and I have the data to back I up and say, like, that person answered like 200 other student's questions and you're right on the border, then occasionally we'll bump people.
数据显示，比如那个人回答了200个其他学生的问题，我们会考虑网开一面
But it is exceedingly rare.
但这是极其罕见的
So you should think of these as pretty much what your score is going to be.
所以这就是你的分数
I don't do the thing that some classes do where at the end of the semester I say,
我不会做某些课程在学期末会做的事情，比如
oh, well, we don't have enough As.
我们 A 的名额不够了
So I'm going to lower all the bends and Cs and so forth.
所以要降低所有的分数段，以此类推
I mean, I will if it goes really badly, like we really screw up writing the exam,
但如果真的很糟糕，比如我们真的把考试写得一团糟，我会修改
or you guys perform differently than we expect.
或者你们的表现和我们预期的不一样
But in the last two times I've taught this class,
但在最近两次我教这门课的时候
I haven't had to change the bends.
没有改变分数段的需要
So for the most part, the bends I anticipate, assuming that we do everything right,
所以一般情况下，假设我们预算的分数段是正确的
that this should be the way the grades come out.
这应该就是分数出来的方式
I will definitely not make the grades any worse.
我绝对不会让成绩变得更糟
So if it turns out that we accidentally make the exams too easy, then people accidentally get grades that are too high.
如果我们不小心把考试搞得太简单了，那么学生就会意外地得到过高的分数
But you should consider yourself the goals you're striving for are the ones on the site and plan accordingly.
但是你应该考虑自己的目标，并做相应的计划
So as far as the course goes, we're going to start off real quick.
我们的课程进度很快
We already have a homework zero that's out.
作业0已经发布了
And you really should be working on it.
你真的应该下功夫了
If you haven't done it yet, I highly encourage you to do it before your lab if it's not too late,
如果你还没有做，我强烈建议你在实验之前做，希望我提醒的不算晚
and especially before you watch the second lecture.
尤其是在你看第二节课之前
Because I'm not going to go through and explain like this is the while loop, this is an if statement and everything.
因为我不会解释 while 循环、if 语句这些基本的东西
Because you've done that before.
你之前肯定做过
And this is your chance to actually see what it looks like on your own.
这是你亲眼看看它是什么样子的机会
One of the things I really, really want to encourage you to do in this class is experiment.
我真的想鼓励你们在这节课上做的一件事就是实验
You're not going to explode your computer.
你不会炸毁你的电脑的
You may as well try things out.
你不妨试试看
Because I want you to be able to go out there and do the things you want to do without having to get help from someone.
因为我希望你能够做你想做的事情，而不需要得到别人的帮助
We're still going to give you help, because this is a very hard class.
这是一门非常难的课，我们仍然会给你们帮助
But it will be important for you to really push yourself to the limits before you come and ask for help.
不过一定要尽全力后再来寻求帮助
Not because we don't want to, but because it's good for you.
这样做对你有好处
Then the other thing going on now is we have labs this first week.
当前的另一件事第一周的实验
So Lab 1 is how to use the various tools, which is the Java compiler and the Git version control software.
实验1将介绍如何使用各种工具，即 Java 编译器和 Git 版本控制软件
And you're going to hate Git at first. I'm just going to tell you.
一开始你会很讨厌 Git
But you'll get used to it.
但你会习惯的
Everybody else has.
每个人都有这个过程
Maybe someday there will be a slightly better abstraction we all agree on for how version control should work.
也许有一天会有个更抽象、我们都能理解的版本控制工具
But till then, Git's the story.
但在那之前还是使用 Git 吧
And then we have Lab 1B.
之后我们有实验1B
So you should do this actually before Lab 1 despite the weird naming if you want to do work on your own computer, which is pretty much everybody.
所以如果你想在自己电脑上工作，你应该在实验1之前完成
So this lets you set up all the software on your computer.
这个作业可以设置计算机上的所有软件
But if you run into any hitches, we'll be there in lab.
如果有麻烦，我们在实验室等你
One exception to what I was saying earlier about trying to explore on your own, with Lab 1 and Lab 1B,
除了之前说的让你们独自探索的实验1和实验1B
there's a lot of pitfalls.
这里面有很多陷阱
So definitely ask us questions early when it comes to computer set up stuff.
所以一定尽早提问电脑设置的问题
Because unlike programming languages which you do have experience with,
这跟学习编程语言不同
with computer set up there's all kinds of annoying things that can happen.
设置电脑可能引起很烦的事情
And I don't want you to waste like three hours of your day trying to get installed something.
我不想你因为安装软件一天浪费三四个小时
So definitely talk to us about computer setup issues ASAP.
所以尽早告诉我们有关电脑设置的问题
Project zero will be released Friday.
项目0将于周五发布
That is the date of that second lecture.
也就是上第二堂课那天
And it will be due a week later.
项目将在一周后到期
So you get seven days to do this project.
也就是说你有7天时间完成
And it's going to be a chance to use all of the basic features of Java to build a gravity simulator where you can watch planets orbiting in space.
你将有机会使用 Java 的所有基本功能来建立一个重力模拟器，
从而观察到在太空中运行的行星
And in this project, you're allowed to work in pairs.
在这个项目中你们可以结对工作
I'll talk a little bit more on Friday about how those pairs work.
周五我会更详细地谈一谈如何结对工作
But the key rule here is you cannot work with somebody who's taken a Java class if you've not.
关键是如果你不懂 Java 就无法跟使用 Java 的人合作
So you either need to both have taken a Java class or both not have taken a Java class.
所以要么两个人都使用 Java 要么两个人都不使用
And so we'll have a form that we'll send out,
我们会发出一张表格
so you can sign up and set up your partnerships.
你可以登记寻找你的伙伴
So in the next video, which I actually recorded--
所以在我录制的下一段视频中--
let's see, August, September, October, November, December-- six months ago, we'll do our first programming assignment.
让我们看看 八月、九月、十月、十一月、十二月--六个月前 我们将完成我们的第一个编程作业
So now let's step backwards in time and see younger me tell you about your first Java program.
现在我们倒退一步，让那时的我给你讲第一个 Java 程序
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）